[Music]
hey everyone and welcome
back don't forget Tobe and hit the
notification
updated so for today's video we're going
to make a product review
about a beauty skin care from B
b i s a a
r this is a sunscreen SPF oil 3E 90 SPF
90 and here's how it looks
like actually
another uh product NG spf50 NG
V pero mag warning AK
approve
V like FDA
warning February 2022 and then the next
one is June 2022 so both SPF 90 and SPF
50 of this
V warning against the use of this
product
approve resarch
this is from guangzu like pro beauty
cosmetics
Co yeah this this product is made in
China as a navigator browser search and
then I discovered
now this one is actually safe Naman to
use I'm not saying it B because this not
sponsor b as a sample for for me to
review
butare Lang AKO thoughts about it and
search and this product has been
circulating like around the
world
China bent SI sa Alibaba and then pan y
live proof warning FP website live pro
and
the product and the product
ala par something dollar
price but yeah
Naman this one is too
cheap Okay so T try nin
too nagay K ano sa
M this is my be face
and so now I'm going to take off my
eyelasses I can't see your
CLE okay so Ayan ulit siya Hy
nakikita Kasi inted soan KO n NG
icon and by the way this product is 40 G
Yung Gano ni is 40 G per wal sample NG
SPF 50 SPF 90
langon zero air bacteria and
Sabio ano SI sunscreen for the best
protection and
coverage Kasi instant protection and
foundation
so okay let's try it B ginagamit sa
AB so
yeah
sh oily sh paraang ointment oint KAS May
oil cream par
lotion
sticky I think it's an O based product
Sabi KAS
is oil free sunscreen though per most of
the sunscreen Nam talaga is parang
oily protect face
UV UV I UV
wow Foundation
effect so let's
see forward
is
sticky like
Mal para Lang Naman siyang
lotion Paras Nam sunscreen D
rejuvenating
set
and sa Amo Naman Niya is mild Lang Yung
scent
Niya and
me
glue SC and it's
Toler it's
affordable per talaga it's safe to
use
alipas so sain KO okay siya may light
coverage
sh
J full coverage parang instant makeup
but this one has light coverage Pam
primer before
makeup Kasi May
oil
magles so sa update Kay
after nagamit for like a week G andab KO
sa
is and scent is scent
Lang and Yung price ni Pala nto I 49
pesos 40 g n to it cost like 40 pesos 49
pesos and then 79 pesos na buy 1 take
one
so description box y link ni sa shoe and
then Magan AKO sa Tik to para
Mak
actually matagal na Kasi to KAS
Lang Kasi it's for free y
but para sa Akin
is to use
para light Lang oil
ni and Ayan siy ay pero P ano Pala NATO
Pala siy hindiya Mas oily oily Lang Pala
talaga nilagay Mo kasiyan SI para AK my
S powder and S Foundation check Naman
for me and
and
a is okay P
Na
and
questions comment section open in
comment section and I guess it can help
you and thank you guys for watching
don't forget to like subscribe and hit
the notification for updated my videos
and see you guys next time
[Music]
bye